financialpanther.com 2019-05-16

# Privacy Policy - Financial Panther

Financial Panther found at https://www.financialpanther.com/ (“Website”) is governed by the following privacy policy (“Privacy Policy”).

We respect your privacy and are committed to protecting it. The purpose of this Privacy Policy is to inform you as to what personally identifiable information we may collect and how it may be used. This statement only applies to this Website. By using this Website, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.

**Collection of your Personal Information**

We do not collect personally identifiable information from our users. We may gather personal or non-personal information in the future.

Information about your computer hardware and software may be automatically collected by the Website. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring website addresses. This information is used for the operation of the Website, to maintain the quality of the Website, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the Website.

Please keep in mind that if you directly disclose personally identifiable information or personally sensitive data through the Website’s public message boards (post & comments), this information may be collected and used by others.

The Website encourages you to review the privacy statements of websites you choose to link to from the Website so that you can understand how those websites collect, use, and share your information. The Website is not responsible for the privacy statements or other content on websites outside of this Website.

**Opt-Out & Unsubscribe**

We respect your privacy and give you an opportunity to opt-out of receiving announcements of certain information. Users may opt-out of receiving any or all communications from the Website by unsubscribing via email or by contacting the webmaster at the contact information below.

**Changes to this Statement**

The Website will occasionally update this Privacy Policy to reflect company and customer feedback. The Website encourages you to periodically review this Privacy Policy to be informed of how the Website is protecting your information.

This Site is affiliated with AdThrive, LLC (“AdThrive”) for the purposes of placing advertising on the Site.  AdThrive uses standard and widely-available tools for the placement and serving of ads, including those provided by Google, Inc. and its affiliates. We publish interest-based advertisements on the Site; that is, ads that are tailored to reflect your interests. To help understand your interests, AdThrive, Google and our other advertising partners will track your behaviour on our website and on other websites across the Internet using cookies.  

A cookie is a file containing an identifier (a string of letters and numbers) that is sent by a web server to a web browser and is stored by the browser. The identifier is then sent back to the server each time the browser requests a page from the server. Cookies may be either “persistent” cookies or “session” cookies: a persistent cookie will be stored by a web browser and will remain valid until its set expiry date, unless deleted by the user before the expiry date; a session cookie, on the other hand, will expire at the end of the user session, when the web browser is closed.  Cookies do not typically contain any information that personally identifies a user, but personal information that we store about you may be linked to the information stored in and obtained from cookies.

By using this Site, you consent to the use of such cookies and the sharing of data captured by such cookies with AdThrive, Google, and our other third party partners. You can view, delete or add interest categories associated with your browser by visiting: [https://adssettings.google.com](https://adssettings.google.com/). You can also opt out of the network cookie using those settings or using the Network Advertising Initiative’s multi-cookie opt-out mechanism at: [http://optout.networkadvertising.org](http://optout.networkadvertising.org/). However, these opt-out mechanisms themselves use cookies, and if you clear the cookies from your browser your opt-out will not be maintained.  

For European Economic Area Residents

If you reside in a country in the European Economic Area (EEA), then under the GDPR and applicable data protection laws you have the rights, among other things, to access your personal data, have us erase it, and/or restrict its further processing.  If you wish to access or delete your personal data (if any) maintained by us or AdThrive related to advertising on the Site, you can contact us at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) and contact AdThrive at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#9ef7f0f8f1defffaeaf6ecf7e8fbb0fdf1f3). If you wish to see a list of the advertising partners we work with or change which of those partners track your behavior using cookies, click the ad preferences link at the bottom of the site. (Available in the EU.)

**Contact Information**

At any time, please contact us at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) for questions related to this Privacy Policy.

LAST UPDATED: Feb 15, 2019
